

Be'er Sheva. Israel

📳 +972527044577 | 🗷 lubacareer@gmail.com | 🧥 https://my-portfolio-alpha-ten-93.vercel.app/ | 🖸 github.com/lubani | 🛅 luba-ira

Objective

As a Software Engineering master's degree graduate with a solid foundation in software development principles, I am on the verge of completing an extracurricular course with DevOps as its main topic. My research has delved into the complexities of the Stefan Problem and heat transfer in lunar regolith, showcasing my ability to tackle intricate problems and contribute to advanced computational modeling projects. With a keen eye for detail and a rigorous approach to software design and implementation, I am well-prepared to contribute to a broad range of technical disciplines. My GitHub and Portfolio website showcase a breadth of projects that demonstrate versatility and commitment to hands-on learning. My tutoring experience has honed my ability to demystify complex concepts, preparing me to contribute effectively to multidisciplinary teams.

Education

Experts Group 2023 – 2024

DEVOPS COURSE

• Studied hands-on DevOps topics with coursework and projects.

Sami Shamoon College of Engineering

2022 - 2024

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

- Thesis: Modeling and Simulation of the 2-Phase Stefan Problem for Lunar Regolith Melting
- · Relevant Coursework: Deep Learning, Advanced Algorithms, Data Structures, NLP, Computer Vision, Advanced Databases
- GPA: 96

Sami Shamoon College of Engineering

2015 - 202

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

- Final Project: Summarization of Hebrew text using NLP techniques
- GPA: 80

Technical Skills

Programming Languages Python, Java, C++, C, C#, SQL, R, HTML, CSS

Tools & Environments UNIX systems, Git, Docker, PyCharm, Visual Studio, CLion, Lex/Flex, Yacc/Bison

Frameworks & Libraries TensorFlow, OpenCV, Django, Matplotlib, Keras, Tkinter

Software Development SDLC methodologies (Waterfall, Agile, Kanban, Scrum), CI/CD principles

Professional Experience

Aleh Association September 2023 – May 2024

TUTOR/TRANSCRIBER

- Enhanced disabled students understand course topics through tutoring.
- · Accurately transcribed lessons for accessibility.

Sami Shamoon College of Engineering

April 2023 - May 2024

Tutor

• Tutored various courses in the Software Engineering department, for both individuals and groups.

AllRight LTD November 2023 – February 2024

ENGLISH TEACHER FOR KIDS

 $\bullet \ \ \ \ \text{Conducted engaging English lessons for children, adapting to diverse learning styles}.$

Achva Academic College

November 2021 - April 2022

TUTOR

• Practiced the databases course for students in the Information Systems department.

Research Experience __

Sami Shamoon College of Engineering

2022 - 2024

STUDENT ON A RESEARCH TRACK

- Developed a computational model for simulating lunar regolith melting.
- Utilized Python 3 for creating numerical simulations of heat transfer.
- · Used numerical and analytical methods as gold standard for a Physics-Informed Neural Network to solve the same problem.

Projects

Personal Project 2023

DEVOPS PROJECT

- Developed hands-on exercises and real-world projects related to DevOps practices and tools.
- Covered topics such as CI/CD pipelines, containerization with Docker, orchestration with Kubernetes, and infrastructure as code using Terraform and Ansible.
- GitHub: DevOps2412

Master's Research Project

2023

SCIENTIFIC PROJECT: 2-PHASE STEFAN PROBLEM

- Focused on the 2-phase Stefan problem using Python 3 and a Physics-Informed Neural Network (PINN).
- · Developed numerical simulations for melting and solidification processes of iron on Earth and regolith on the Moon.
- GitHub: scientificProject

Personal Project 2023

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

- Developed a personal portfolio website using Next. js and Tailwind CSS.
- Showcased personal projects and professional experience.
- · Official: Portfolio
- · GitHub: Source code

Personal Project 2023

SOLVING MATH PROBLEMS

- Developed solutions for problems in Probability, Statistics, Calculus, and Algorithms.
- · GitHub: math

Bachelor's Final Project

2022

HEBREW TEXT SUMMARIZER

- Developed a Hebrew text summarizer browser extension.
- Used JavaScript, JSON, HTML, Python, PyTorch, Transformers, Flask, and HTML in the implementation.
- GitHub: Summarizer-Extension (Old)
- GitHub: HebSum (New)

Master's Coursework

2023

INFORMATION RETRIEVAL COURSE

- Developed Python programs for Sentiment Analysis and Abstractive Summarization.
- · GitHub: IRCourse

Master's Coursework

2023

MICROSERVICES PROJECT

- Developed a microservices project using Django, PostgreSQL, and Prometheus.
- · GitHub: DjangoMS

Languages

English Native-level proficiency **Hebrew** Native proficiency

Russian Native speaker, intermediate reading and writing

Extracurricular Activities

- Practicing Yoga
- Listening to Audiobooks
- Following Educational Podcasts